{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What player had the following stat line: 0 points, 28 total rebounds, 10 offensive boards, and 3 assists?",
            "options": ["Dwight Howard", "Andre Drummond", "DeAndre Jordan", "Dennis Rodman"],
            "answer": "Dennis Rodman"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the only person to win the MVP, Coach of the Year & Executive of the Year?",
            "options": ["Pat Riley", "Larry Bird", "Phil Jackson", "Red Auerbach"],
            "answer": "Larry Bird"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who drafted Kobe Bryant straight out of High School in 1996?",
            "options": ["Los Angeles Lakers", "Charlotte Hornets (He was then traded to the Lakers)", "Orlando Magic", "Chicago Bulls"],
            "answer": "Charlotte Hornets (He was then traded to the Lakers)"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many years do players need to be retired before being eligible for Hall of Fame induction?",
            "options": ["2 years", "3 years", "4 years", "5 years"],
            "answer": "5 years"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which NBA player is known as 'The Admiral'?",
            "options": ["Shaquille O'Neal", "David Robinson", "Tim Duncan", "Hakeem Olajuwon"],
            "answer": "David Robinson"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the longest winning streak in NBA history?",
            "options": ["28 games by the 2012/13 Miami Heat", "33 games by the 1971/72 Lakers", "20 games by the 2015/16 Golden State Warriors", "26 games by the 1970/71 Milwaukee Bucks"],
            "answer": "33 games by the 1971/72 Lakers"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which player won the 2000 Slam Dunk Contest?",
            "options": ["Vince Carter", "Tracy McGrady", "Kobe Bryant", "Allen Iverson"],
            "answer": "Vince Carter"
        },
        {
            "question": "What jersey numbers did Michael Jordan wear for the Bulls?",
            "options": ["23, 45 & 12 (12 for 1 game after his jersey was stolen before the game)", "8 & 24", "9 & 33", "3 & 6"],
            "answer": "23, 45 & 12 (12 for 1 game after his jersey was stolen before the game)"
        },
        {
            "question": "In which NBA season did Kyle Korver achieve his best three-point percentage, shooting an impressive 53.6 percent?",
            "options": ["2007-08", "2012-13", "2015-16", "2009-10"],
            "answer": "2009-10"
        },
        {
            "question": "What US state has produced the most NBA players?",
            "options": ["California", "Texas", "New York", "Florida"],
            "answer": "California"
        }
    ]
}
